The global mood is quite good, there is
no change, the market is
trading with a slight decline, the market is flat, the
European markets are seeing a rise of half a percent, along with this the
US 10 year
bond is near 1.18 percent,
you do not see any major movement there, there is a
slight pressure on the dollar, but
see that no major action role is
seen in the market, it is a record,
but what to do, the position should be maintained till then,
Deep, there is no special problem,
if you want to gym first, then
buy a crow pre-vote option of 16000, it
is below this and will maintain its bullish position,
then you can give 16500 equal option,
no question, the bank
Nifty is ready to give above 6000
and exhausted doing, if it
comes above your Chhattisgarh, then there is nothing to worry about, there will be a
little Chhattisgarh mark in the coming minutes,
but there is nothing to be afraid, the bank
seems to be getting ready for the animals and in this, if you
want in the bank also  If
you buy a full stock around 35,500, then if there is an
unexpected fall in America and
gas comes out from today, then it will work magic for you. So
this was between the bank 36231
440 6236. Jatin was
seen getting ready for more options, so
take the advice of maintaining long position in both because
definitely do it with great speed and you will not have any bad dreams
if you
subscribe to the stock above that.
This message should be sent from the market upwards at 16200. It will
work as a strong support for 1616.
Open interest of 16256 shares and out of that,
48 lakh shares are
blocked in the earlier 16300. Where
28% of this token inter college 64 lakh shares joined today,
then it is different for that that
today will be the saving time in 16,875 16335 serial. So if you people
want to buy profit entry should be made around 16300, then
subscribe. This will happen that
if above Chhattisgarh, then
preparation for a very big one.
Subscribe then get
ready to go to school which can be ready for life time,
like, share and
subscribe, if
above 36036 the bank is ready for clear-cut
nonstop rise, it will be
written and then you have to move ahead by trailing stop loss,
you think bank
nifty is also ready, prepare it Deepu, see
after the big day of the first installment, for the
first time a long position has been created in Bangkok when
scooter lighting and see, this is the
press port writing in the range of 35,500 to 36,000